{
	"records":[
		{
			"question":"2 x 1 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 3 =",
			"answer":15
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 4 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 2 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 5 =",
			"answer":15
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 10 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 5 =",
			"answer":5
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 2 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 10 =",
			"answer":50
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 1 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 3 =",
			"answer":9
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 5 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 10 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 5 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 2 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 2 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 5 =",
			"answer":25
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 0 =",
			"answer":0
		}
	]
}